Ori Lazarovitch

- **054-5454116**
- ™ ori10122001@gmail.com
- Tel Aviv
- <u>2001</u>
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/ori-lazarovitch-782561224

Awards

Certificate of Excellence

Mamas course

Skills

- Programming
- SOLID Design Principles
- OOP
- Full Stack Development
- UI + UX
- Python
- React
- Node
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- C# + .NET
- WPF
- MongoDB
- SQL
- GitJira
- Confluence

Languages

Hebrew

English

Spanish

Software developer at IDF – 81 Unit, with 5+ years of experience in programming. Highly motivated, organized, methodological worker, who's always seeking to learn and improve myself and my environment. Proficient in a wide range of technologies and programming languages, keeping up with the latest advancements.

Experience

Software Developer

□ 04/2021 - Present

IDF - 81 Unit

Developed a full stack desktop application which processed, analyzed and rendered data visually.

Tech stack: **WPF** (C#), **Python**, and **MongoDB**.

Software Developer

[□] 08/2019 - 04/2021

Rafael

♥ Kiryat Bialik

Developed a full stack web application which helped cyber defenders manage and handle possible attacks more efficiently.

Tech stack: React, Node, and PostgreSQL.

Education

B.Sc in Computer Science

□ 12/2023 - Present

Israeli Military Intelligence

Mamas (Gamma) cyber course

[□] 04/2021 - 08/2021

Israeli Military Intelligence

Cyber Program

[□] 10/2017 - 07/2020

Magshimim - National Cyber Education Program

♥ Emek Izrael

Projects

PIPL – Website (inside 81 Unit's network)

□ 11/2021 – Present

Outside of my daily job, two friends and I developed a web application that makes searching for people, teams, and departments easier than ever.

Tech stack: React (Typescript), Python, and MongoDB.